<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://sourcecrypto.pub/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://sourcecrypto.pub/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-06-11T01:27:42-04:00</updated><id>https://sourcecrypto.pub/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Source Crypto</title><subtitle>Chat Server for Creating an Open-Source Database of Crypto Knowledge.</subtitle><author><name>⧉ Infominer</name></author><entry><title type="html">Testing out the Blog Feed.</title><link href="https://sourcecrypto.pub/welcome-blog-feed/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Testing out the Blog Feed." /><published>2019-05-29T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2019-05-29T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://sourcecrypto.pub/blog-source</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sourcecrypto.pub/welcome-blog-feed/">&lt;p&gt;It’s safe to say that I’m testing the limits of the Minimal Mistakes theme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I decided to try out the blog format, mostly just to see if it would work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A neat thing w blogs, is by using tags and categories there are many different ways to display and interact with the content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found out that using too many collections will break this theme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;notice--success&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I just updated this index, because I knew there was a ton of value hidden away in the discord server. I can see, also, that these pages are showing up in search, and that folk are making use. YAY!  You may have noticed the navigation was broken for a day while updating… apparently Jekyll doesn’t like more than 10 collections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Collections are a simple way to throw a bunch of similar type of documents in a directory and display them together, without a bunch of manual labor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I expanded to 12 categories, and it broke.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, I dropped back to 9 and nav came back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I wanted to see if I started a blog would the site still work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9 categories and a blog are ok…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s a lot of ways to organize information :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I doubt I’ll stick with the post index home page for long, since I don’t expect to be blogging here, much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it’s good to know I can, and this is where any long serious crypto articles I write would live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-pax&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>⧉ Infominer</name></author><summary type="html">It’s safe to say that I’m testing the limits of the Minimal Mistakes theme.</summary></entry></feed>